<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Abhijith's BLOG</title><description>The place for and of my thoughts.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>Abhijith's BLOG</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 1.24</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 08:55:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>true-vision</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It doesn't matter if people &lt;strong&gt;praise me&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;curse me&lt;/strong&gt; because in the end, &lt;strong&gt;I know where I stand&lt;/strong&gt; and that's what matters most to me.&lt;br&gt;
They give me shitty value, they praise me to the sky, they ignore me even with me standing infront of them, It never bothers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/06/12/true-vision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1f737576281707ea854f53</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 08:33:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It doesn't matter if people &lt;strong&gt;praise me&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;curse me&lt;/strong&gt; because in the end, &lt;strong&gt;I know where I stand&lt;/strong&gt; and that's what matters most to me.&lt;br&gt;
They give me shitty value, they praise me to the sky, they ignore me even with me standing infront of them, It never bothers me and &lt;strong&gt;NEVER WILL&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's like a superhuman power given to me by the lord grace.&lt;br&gt;
I always knew there was a reason why I could always stay away from all this praises and curses and maybe just maybe I wasn't the one who was worth all those.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel happy at times for myself but never too boastful about what I did good or bad. Others' feeling on those never gave me joy but my satisfaction on what I did gave me joy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wish that super human power never leave me with time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>F.R.I.E.N.D.S</title><description>Not your fault maybe.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/06/06/f-r-i-e-n-d-s/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba3e</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 16:01:47 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/f533c22f0751b5c294b499f978295273--box-friends.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/f533c22f0751b5c294b499f978295273--box-friends.jpg" alt="F.R.I.E.N.D.S"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Relax it's not about the American epic dramatic TV show. But I wish things were like that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm probably not in a terrific mood today. Trust me I have my reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know what I realized, &lt;strong&gt;You don't call friends &amp;quot;friends&amp;quot; when you gotta tell them what and why it is about even before calling them.&lt;br&gt;
You call them friends when they pick up your line and starts listening with their full attention and give you their full ears without hesitating and most importantly not raising the &lt;em&gt;Why?&lt;/em&gt; question.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe it isn't their fault after all. It might be yours. How right!&lt;br&gt;
for starters, it was you who thought and called them 'friends' in the first place. Bad luck boy. It is you whose choices that made every change to this point. If you drifted away from that particular moment that made you to meet and slowly become friends, you wouldn't have become their friend and probably wouldn't have gotten this hurt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time isn't it. Slow as a snail and yet powerful as a knife.&lt;br&gt;
No one asked you for anything and still why are you expecting those from the ones you call friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't say every one of your friends are like that. Some doesn't bother your call and even loves to talk to you even if they're occupied with their things, and there're some who wouldn't mind calling you back as soon as you leave a missed call.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deal with it bro. You're the one who failed in choosing the so called right 'friends' and it is not your fault you don't have a friendship like the 6 had in F.R.I.E.N.D.S.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any Regrets? I would say NEVER coz even though everything seems out of place, We're friends and will always be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;n.b. this was purely about me and me only. I think I criticized myself. Screw it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>untitled</title><description>Whether you should or not. Read more..</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/04/26/untitled/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba3c</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 03:59:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; live a life that you may wanna live to please all the people in the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; do things for the people who can go behind your back.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; swim ocean for people who won't even cross a bridge for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; trust everyone blindly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; expect things from everyone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; be friends mean people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You &lt;strong&gt;shouldn't&lt;/strong&gt; love anyone unconditionally but yourself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You &lt;strong&gt;shouldn't&lt;/strong&gt; feel pain in anyway.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You wanna know why!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You should live a life that you may wanna live to please all the people in the world &lt;strong&gt;then only you'll understand that there's more to life much more enjoyable than living a life to please everyone.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You should do things for the people who can go behind your back &lt;strong&gt;that makes you understand people's true double faced fickle mindedness.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You should swim ocean for people who won't even cross a bridge for you &lt;strong&gt;that way reality hits and leaves you broken like the leaf fell from the tree.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You should trust everyone blindly &lt;strong&gt;that way you'll know the pain that comes with it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You should expect things from everyone &lt;strong&gt;which when they fail you, you get to know that expectations hurt and things n people are temporary.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You should be friends with mean people &lt;strong&gt;as then you can see how ruthlessly they can bring you to rockbottom.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You shouldn't love anyone unconditionally but yourself &lt;strong&gt;that way when people you love leave you, you won't be left in vain.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You shouldn't feel pain in anyway coz if you do feel it, it'll make you &lt;strong&gt;do&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;dont's&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;not do&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;do's&lt;/strong&gt; as I told here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do/Don't.&lt;br&gt;
It's our choice that leads life to take turns.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Choose happiness over anything. In the end it is what matters and &lt;strong&gt;you&lt;/strong&gt; of all the people in world &lt;strong&gt;deserve to love and to be loved to the fullest.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Faces</title><description>Blog Post about Peoples' faces. Read more..</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/04/22/faces/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba3b</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 15:06:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://localhost:2368/2018/04/22/faces/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Strange thing happened today. &lt;strong&gt;I forgot faces.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Sounds funny I know but it's true and quite a lot embarrassing.&lt;br&gt;
How can I forget faces of people I know or at least I used to know so easily at my 20's!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was embarrassed when those 2 friends asked me if I didn't recognise them at all. One of them I see usually in the bus while on the way to college and the other I see while on bus back to home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seriously this is the second time I'm up with this issue.&lt;br&gt;
Am I forgetting things so easily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can't say I didn't expect this as nowadays I spend most of the time in my room engaging in things I love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Embarrassing was it, quite embarrassing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may be wondering why write a blog for this right!&lt;br&gt;
WHOOPAH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Pity, Sorry, Forgive</title><description>Justice for Asifa</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/04/13/pity-sorry-forgive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba3a</guid><category>JusticeForAsifa</category><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:07:11 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/GBWA-20180412233705.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/GBWA-20180412233705.jpg" alt="Pity, Sorry, Forgive"&gt;&lt;p&gt;yet another &lt;strong&gt;hashtag&lt;/strong&gt; added to the list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AND?? &lt;em&gt;Is this cycle gonna end someday!!!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So we want &lt;em&gt;our country&lt;/em&gt; to be &lt;em&gt;known for&lt;/em&gt; this kinda &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;shame&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;! &lt;em&gt;Alright then&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUMB COUNTRY&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;FILTHY MUD-HEAD B*tches&lt;/strong&gt; as of now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/GBWA-20180413143647-01.jpg" alt="Pity, Sorry, Forgive"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;she was just an 8 year old and you all did this to her, that poor little girl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Pity&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; on you all&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What if it happened to your child instead!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not just you few who did this to her, we all were a part of the unfortunate crime. We chose this to happen when we were busy planning on making Huge Statues of the dead, fighting over parties, instead of thinking about to make for the betterment and safety. &lt;strong&gt;Alas!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Sorry&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; that we did this to you sister&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Too bad that our mind is so dark that our actions drive us to what we do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;They say it is what it is and what’s done is done but why is it still not changing considering this, not the first time in India&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Forgive&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt; us for what’s done&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Too much to wish for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;But forgive us for being the reason that you went through this misery at this age.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Forgive us for crushing your poor soul, taking the life out of you child.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Is this going to be the last&lt;/em&gt;? I presume not coz &lt;strong&gt;it’s our country&lt;/strong&gt; after all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-&amp;gt; &lt;em&gt;Don’t make this about about just the government or the parties.&lt;br&gt;
-&amp;gt; Don’t make this about Men vs Women.&lt;br&gt;
-&amp;gt; Make this about &lt;strong&gt;Us&lt;/strong&gt; against the monsters out there within us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I seriously can’t bear seeing another picture of you with the pretty face of yours torn apart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;May you rest in peace little sister.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/GBWA-20180413132659.jpg" alt="Pity, Sorry, Forgive"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not gonna use the &lt;strong&gt;J&lt;/strong&gt; word anyway&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-A&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Silence</title><description>Post on Time. Read more..</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/04/02/silence/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba39</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 13:00:40 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/The-clock.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/The-clock.jpg" alt="Silence"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The word so close to &lt;strong&gt;Fear&lt;/strong&gt;, or maybe that which troubles us to feel fear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the whole world stands still and then we hear the &lt;em&gt;clock’s ticking&lt;/em&gt;, that when &lt;strong&gt;dark&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;em&gt;shades our mind&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;fear&lt;/strong&gt; takes it as a whole making us &lt;em&gt;see&lt;/em&gt; where we &lt;strong&gt;stand&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZJkamsEwato?rel=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the &lt;strong&gt;silence&lt;/strong&gt; hits our ears, shall we have a feeling of &lt;em&gt;something strange&lt;/em&gt;, or the sense of &lt;em&gt;wrong,&lt;/em&gt; dripping with &lt;strong&gt;perspiration&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has it ever occurred to you something like that, like when it’s all silent around you and then you starts to sweat and some thoughts starts rushing to your mind from nowhere, making you feel like you’re lost and left far behind everything?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I have had that sensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listen to the silence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;ehh listen to silence huh? You probably are wondering.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yeah&lt;/strong&gt; there’s a lot of voice within the silence but shall only be heard by the one’s who’s actually listening to the silence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There shall be no fear in the mist of silence if you of all are going with it&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–&lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>F Me</title><description>Blog Post on Peoples' priorities. Read more..</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/03/31/f-me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba38</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 14:35:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Priories&lt;/strong&gt;, The Only f’kin thing that &lt;em&gt;matters&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thing that &lt;em&gt;tears&lt;/em&gt; the paper apart&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Too bad everyone’s a part of this so called era of &lt;em&gt;priorities&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;selfishness&lt;/em&gt;, and most importantly the era where people take &lt;strong&gt;things for granted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should’ve known that all are &lt;em&gt;same&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One I love told me to find someone &lt;em&gt;worthy&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;to talk to.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Too bad I lost her &lt;strong&gt;too&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let her have her priorities seeking what’s best for her, I don’t complain&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wish I knew it sooner &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; it is what it is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;su*ks&lt;/strong&gt; isn’t it when the world you see just &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;flip&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; with you standing there unaffected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The turns life take, &lt;strong&gt;Awesome&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the best to &lt;strong&gt;me&lt;/strong&gt; in finding the things I seek in the random distorted world with so called prioritizing creatures&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Life &lt;strong&gt;su*ks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trust me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Life fkin sucks&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–&lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>headstart</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It all just takes a little pushing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you’ll never know when life would take a turn&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–&lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/03/29/headstart/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba37</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 08:52:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It all just takes a little pushing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you’ll never know when life would take a turn&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–&lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Each sec counts</title><description>Damn it. It's like every second can make a big difference. Read more..</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/03/26/each-sec-counts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba36</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I was all down since yesterday.&lt;/em&gt; There’re many reasons but this has not been happened since a long time as far I can remember. But I found a way out of this which I’m going through. I know no one cares and I’m okay with it. But what happened today is that I gave more time to think of the coming things I can gain if I prepare instead of the things I lost which obviously was my fault in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Take a leap right! Coz we’ll never know where life takes a turn&lt;/em&gt; and I'm going with it to wherever it takes me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Embrace</title><description>A poem written by Divya, a friend of mine from *College of Engg. Pathanapuram. Read more..</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/03/25/poemofdivya/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba35</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 05:45:53 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/J.K.-Rowling-quote-You-control-your-own-life-2.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/J.K.-Rowling-quote-You-control-your-own-life-2.jpg" alt="Embrace"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A poem written by &lt;strong&gt;Divya&lt;/strong&gt;, a friend of mine from &lt;em&gt;College of Engg. Pathanapuram&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/IMG-20180324-WA0006.jpg" alt="Embrace"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason I posted this is that I felt her &lt;em&gt;lines&lt;/em&gt; sort of resembling my life too somehow 🙂&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Damn</title><description>Failure. Read more..</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/03/24/damn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba34</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 18:15:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I failed &lt;strong&gt;AGAIN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I &lt;strong&gt;LOST AGAIN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I should’ve &lt;strong&gt;listened&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overconfidence.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; I feel bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I will do it &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AGAIN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; till I gain what I lost 🙂&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not out of overconfidence but out of the shame I feel for myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–&lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>The pursuit of Happiness</title><description>The long run. Read more..</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/03/23/if-you-can-i-can-too-if-i-can-you-can-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba33</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 16:18:03 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/The-Pursuit-of-Happyness-Screencaps-movies-1814250-720-480.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/06/The-Pursuit-of-Happyness-Screencaps-movies-1814250-720-480.jpg" alt="The pursuit of Happiness"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s with great happiness that find myself writing this. I never thought I could perform a &lt;em&gt;bit better&lt;/em&gt; than I used to be in one of the game which I &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; was &lt;strong&gt;afraid&lt;/strong&gt; of. By afraid I mean It’s a game with a lot of co-players you know, so everytime I make a fool of myself in front of everyone, I somehow actually made my mind to hate the game slowly. But guess what, with all the &lt;em&gt;teasing&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;insulting&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;criticizing&lt;/em&gt;, I’m now starting to learn more and trying to be much focussed at instants. &lt;em&gt;Kidding though.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That doesn’t mean I’m way better now. &lt;strong&gt;🙂&lt;/strong&gt; I’m trying at least.&lt;em&gt;(lol)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe just maybe, someday I could look back and say &lt;strong&gt;Hey I wasn’t AFRAID….&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–&lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>living as I like a.k.a Life is awesome</title><description>Self introspection. Read more..</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/03/21/living-as-i-like-a-k-a-life-is-awesome/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba32</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 07:56:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Did I make a mistake on living like the way I want to rather than looking for from the people? &lt;em&gt;I guess not&lt;/em&gt; but still Why do I feel like I’m lot behind all and I lost self-respect!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I’m not a big fan of people living on others words and choices.&lt;/strong&gt; Also I’m not a big fan of people intruding in others life and &lt;em&gt;judging others’ actions&lt;/em&gt; and all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why don’t they look for themselves and lead a good life!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is that they’re gaining from these kinda sadist attitude, &lt;em&gt;guess I’ll never know.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;btw people have a perception about me that &lt;strong&gt;I FLAUNT&lt;/strong&gt; too much, hehe lol 🙂 Maybe they’re right or maybe they’re wrong but &lt;strong&gt;what gives!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It’s only a life that’s given to us, so why not use it to the fullest!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;flaunt a little, enjoy a little, be crazy for a little, and moreover live the way you like.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-A&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>H3llo W0rld!!</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voila!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is my &lt;em&gt;first&lt;/em&gt; Blog Post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more 🙂&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/03/19/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5b1adcceef88620bc262ba31</guid><dc:creator>Abhijith Vijayan</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 16:19:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voila!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is my &lt;em&gt;first&lt;/em&gt; Blog Post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more 🙂&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>